etfdailynews.com 2015-06-08

# PRIVACY POLICY | ETF DAILY NEWS

## **Privacy Policy:**

Your privacy on the Internet is important to us. As part of the operation of our site, we gather certain types of information about our users, and we would like to explain the types of information we gather, what we do with it and how to correct or change the information.

**Information Collected by This Site**

We collect two types of personally identifying information from users: personal data (such as names and e-mail addresses); and aggregated data (such as information about traffic patterns on the site, for example how many users log into the site on a daily basis).

**Personal Data**

Personal data is collected when users provide personal data to the site. For example in registering for email notification services, answering surveys, purchasing items from the site, sending email to the site, registering for contests and other promotional opportunities, message boards and chat areas.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children (defined herein as minors younger than 13 years of age) without obtaining parental consent. Before registering for an account to use the services of the Web site, we ask that all minors have their parents read our Privacy Policy. Before and during the registration process, we encourage all minors to include a parent or guardian in the process.

**Aggregate Data**

When visitors come to the Web site, we collect and aggregate information indicating, among other things, which pages were visited, and which hyperlinks were “clicked.” Collecting such information involves the logging of IP addresses, operating system and browser software used by each visitor to the Web site.

The non-personally identifiable information we collect helps us diagnose problems with our server, administer the Web site, identify the most popular areas of the Web site, and determine the effectiveness of our promotional activities. In addition, we may disclose some of this information to advertisers to inform them of the number of people who have seen and/or clicked through their advertisements.

**Who this data may be shared with**

Our site uses both the personal and aggregated information collected for multiple purposes. The information is used to improve the content of the site, to customize the content and/or layout of the site for each individual user and to notify users about updates to the site or promotional offers or opportunities that we believe will be of interest to you.

We share aggregated information collected from the site with third parties for both advertising and promotional purposes. We also provide statistical information based on this data to advertisers and other current and potential business partners.

**Data collection regarding minors**

**Children and Privacy**

We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online, and to be fully familiar with the sites visited by their children. At various places on the sites, we ask whether users are under the age of 18, or 13, for example when requesting personal information from a user, we may ask for parental consent. We rely on users to be truthful in responding to these questions.

**Individuals Under 13**

No information should be submitted to or posted on the site by users under the age of 13 years without consent of their parent or guardian. The site does not provide any personally identifying information, regardless of its source collected from users under the age of 13 to any third party for any purpose whatsoever unless disclosed during collection. Users under the age of 13 are asked not to participate in contests or other promotional opportunities, and the site does not knowingly collect information from users under the age of 13.

**Individuals 13 Through 17**

We request that children under the age of 18 do not submit or post information to the site without a parent or guardian’s consent. The site may collect information, including personally identifying information, from users between the ages of 13 and 17, and this information may be used for marketing and promotional purposes by the site and which may be shared with prescreened third parties, with the permission of the user. A user or their parent or guardian may stop the use – either by e-mail request or by modifying his/her registration information online as described above in “Information Collected by The Site.”

**Cookies**

Our site also uses “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that most major websites write into your hard drive for record keeping purposes when you visit them. Cookies allow a website to measure activity on their site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences, thus allowing you to visit various member-only parts of the site without re-registering. We do not use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Except for personal information voluntarily provided by you (i.e. during membership registration or a contest), we do not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes, and that information is not shared with third parties.

You may occasionally get cookies from advertisers on the site, which is standard on the Internet. These cookies are outside the control of our site, and are not subject to our privacy policy. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you’d prefer, you may be able to set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the site, such as the member-only areas and shopping, contest and game areas, will not function properly if you do so.

**How You can Access or Correct Information**

**(Opt out or unsubscribe functions)**

If you would like to have your personally identifiable information changed or removed from our database, please contact us at webmaster@etfdailynews.com, and we will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request. Keep in mind, however, that there will be residual information that will remain within our databases, access logs, and other records, which may or may not contain such personally identifiable information. The residual information will not be used for commercial purposes; however we reserve the right, from time to time, to recontact former customers or users of this Web site.

**Reader Feedback**

Please remember that information posted to message boards and chat areas becomes public information. Use caution when posting. Users under the age of 18 should be especially careful not to provide any personally identifying information while using chat rooms or message boards. Users of chat rooms and message boards must follow acceptable standards of behavior when posting messages online.

**Links to other sites**

It is important to note that this site contains links to other sites, and that those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as our site. For instance, if you click on an advertisement on the site, this will take you away from the site and to an entirely different site. This can include links from advertisers, content providers and partners who may use the sites’ logo and or style as a result of a co-branding agreement. These sites may send their own cookies to you, and may collect data and make uses of it that the sites would not.

Our web site may contain links to other Internet web sites, including co-branded or other affiliated sites that may or may not be owned or operated by us. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites, including such sites’ use of any information (such as IP number, browser type, or operating system) collected when visitors to the web site click through links to those sites. Even though such information might not identify you personally, we strongly encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of those sites.

**Security**

As effective as any security measure implemented by us may be, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.

**Law Enforcement**

We reserve the right to release any and all information contained within our access logs concerning any visitor or member when that visitor or member is in violation of our Terms of Service or other published guidelines, or partakes (or is reasonably suspected of partaking) in any illegal activity, even without a subpoena, warrant, or other court order, and to release such information in response to discovery requests, or in response to any circumstance which we, in our sole discretion, deem an emergency. We cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who may be using our servers or services for illegal activities. We also reserve the right to report any suspected illegal activity to law enforcement for investigation or prosecution.

**USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE TERMS OF USE AND PRIVACY POLICY.**
